[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOT]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Whoever saved Salvador
is the reason why we're
in this trouble right now!
Find out who he is.
Deborah and I are going
to the NCIA.
Colonel Mariano Zafra.
His son is requesting
your presence.
- Mariano.
- Delgado.
I didn't know
you were still serving.
I'm not surprised
that Victor is your son.
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree
You're disciplining
your favorite agent.
She's not my favorite.
Samantha made a mistake,
and she will be held
accountable for it.
- Django!
- Gabo.
You really won't leave
the poor alone, won't you?
What do you guys want?
Do you want us to wipe
each other out here?!
[PIA] Sir!
Sir, we don't have grounds
to stop them
from talking to Victor Zafra.
Hmm.
That's refreshing.
At least not everyone
at NCIA
has a crooked way of thinking.
You can talk to Victor.
But I have my eyes on you.
Your words don't scare me.
Sir, it's not worth it.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you for
your warm welcome, Delgado!
It's definitely warm.
[PIA] Bring them to Victor.
[AGENT] Yes, ma'am.
Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SEBASTIAN] Sam.
Let's hour together.
I'll drive.
No, Karen is with me.
Oh, you miss her already?
I can move to the back.
No need. We'll go
to the same place anyway.
Let's just meet there.
- Ah--
- Let's go.
[SAM] Let's go,
[MAN] Wake up, Zafra.
[CLATTERING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[HANDCUFF CLICKS]
[CELL DOOR CREAKS]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DEBORAH] Attorney,
you can leave us.
Yes, ma'am.
Why am I not yet released?
We're doing everything we can.
But we don't have
any connections in the NCIA.
Don't worry,
we'll get you out of here.
They caught Mr. Chan.
He can throw us under
the bus anytime!
The plan was to
eliminate him, but...
Lucas couldn't do it.
Lucas was even shot.
Lucas was shot?!
Who did it?!
I'm sure the guy I encountered
has something to do with this.
Have you found him yet?
[DEBORAH SIGHS]
Arturo's searching for him.
He better hide
once I find out who he is.
For now, while we still
don't know who he is,
I'll make sure Mr. Chan
keeps quiet.
Do it, son.
I'll count to three.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Get your guns out!
One!
Two!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Three!
- Wait, Gabo! Wait!
I-I'm not here for you.
We're just trying
to make a living!
We won't fight you, Gabo.
I know you have firearms.
Believe me, Gabo.
Ever since you defeated me...
I never considered
taking revenge!
I thought about our childhood.
Do you remember that?
We were inseparable!
We worked together!
You know, I even helped you!
I hope you don't forget
those days, Gabo!
Gabo, I'm sorry.
I'll let you have this.
If you want, you can bury him.
I-I won't mess with him anymore.
Django.
If I hear that you're still
causing trouble here,
I'll make sure...
that tomorrow...
...you'll be in a coffin.
Okay, Gabo.
Go bury your dad.
- Let's go!
- Let's go, let's go!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TOLITS GRUNTS]
I thought we were going
to fight them.
I was going to use up
all these bullets on Django.
Good thing I controlled myself.
They should be grateful
my head's clear.
They're lucky.
If I used my shotgun...
[IMITATES A GUN]
...they'd be dead.
[TEKLA] You guys, stop it!
You're all so arrogant
when the enemy's gone!
You should be grateful
Django didn't do anything,
or else we'd be the ones dead!
You're not using your heads.
Man, that got me so nervous!
Good thing Django
didn't come back,
or else we're all dead!
They even have firearms!
Gabo, Gabo.
Thank you so much
for helping us.
Gabo. Thank you, thank you.
I can finally bury my husband.
[WOMAN WHIMPERING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Poor Sir Freddo.
Those bastards
really are heartless.
[MONEY RUSTLING]
Miss Lourdes...
- Please excuse our offering.
- Thank you so much, Gabo.
I hope you can finally bury
Sir Freddo.
Thank you, Gabo. Thank you.
- Let's go.
- [TEKLA] Come on.
Stop playing!
[BINOY] Move aside, move aside.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[OLI] Boss, take a look at this.
Don't be embarrassed, Salvador.
Come here!
That's so good, boss.
[SALVADOR] That's the video
I bought.
And there's the man
who saved me.
- He was so brave, boss!
- [OLI] That guy's amazing!
Don't think of him as the star.
I mean, does he pull up
our ratings?
[OLI] Boss is right.
Dude, you're the star.
[ARNEL] This is so good.
We can use this!
[SALVADOR] Boss, I'm the victim.
My image might get ruined
from all that flimsy action.
Dude, stop acting like
you're not in media.
Let's show the people
what they want to see.
[SALVADOR] That man
is the brave and helpful one.
Gabo knocked down the muggers.
I'm just a victim.
Attorney.
If only we had a connection
from the inside...
We wouldn't have
these problems anymore.
Mariano...
The more you look,
the more
our potential allies hide.
If only we had an ally
from the higher-ups.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe you don't have
to look up.
They're probably just close by.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GATES CREAK]
[KEYS JANGLING]
- [LOCK CLANGING]
- [KEYS JANGLING]
[HANDCUFFS CLANKING]
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
[MR. CHAN EXHALES]
Who's your visitor?
Why would you like to know?
I want to know!
We're partners, right?
Are we really allies, Mr. Chan?
Or do you want to rat me out
to save yourself?
I don't know
what you are saying!
Didn't you tell anything
to the NCIA?
Are you threatening me, Victor?!
I told you mouth shut,
no talk!
Why are you mad?
Did you snitch to the NCIA?
No, no!
- [MR. CHAN GROANING]
- [VICTOR GRUNTING]
Stop that!
[POLICE] Call for help!
[OBJECT CLANGS]
[POLICE] Stop that!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- Hey! Stop that! Stop!
- Hey!
[MR. CHAN GROANING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GATE CREAKS]
[LOCK CLANGING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Salvador,
listen to me, alright?
No matter what kind
of story it is,
you should be able
to manipulate it
to be in your favor.
That's the key for your
popularity to skyrocket.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
This will be our pilot episode
for your show.
We'll make it look like
someone tried to kill you.
This better be true, Salvador.
Then, let's say that you
beat those people up.
Wait, boss, hold it right there.
You beat them up.
- But I didn't--
- Yes, you did!
- Alright, I did!
- That's it!
They were no match for you!
Now, you look tough.
Now, you're the hero!
Sounds fantastic.
[ISOBEL] Okay, excuse me, Pinky.
Hi!
General!
Oh, honey!
- General's here.
- Oh, yes! You're early.
Thanks for joining us.
Glad you could make it.
- Vic!
- Evening, General!
Good evening!
What did we miss, General?
Miss?
A lot! Come, take a seat.
Okay. Please, come in.
- Hi!
- [WOMAN] General, hi!
Good evening.
Hello!
I was just telling them
how I got even more blessings
ever since I purchased
Ginintuang Lupa.
The moment Ricardo saw
the potential of the property,
he purchased it right away!
Yes, we are so blessed!
- Yes!
- It's a good investment!
- It is.
But Ricardo,
the demolition
of Ginintuang Lupa
is still making a lot of noise.
Well, that will pass.
I mean, the complaining
of informal settlers
when you try to take
your property
isn't new to us anyway.
Which doesn't belong to them
by the way.
- That's right.
- One way or another,
those informal settlers
will have to leave that place!
Oh, I wish they'd just flee
the place on their own
so that we don't have to swat
those flies away anymore!
[LAUGHTER]
But Ricardo, how's
the development going?
It's a waste of your time
and money
until you don't make use
of that land.
That's true, Vic.
But, you know,
to be honest,
I believe this is one
of my best investments.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know,
for now we're doing
the finishing touches
and then we'll be opening it up
to future investors.
Now,
if you saved up some money
or if you want
to be part of a...
wise investment,
join me. I can assure you,
my project won't fail you.
- Yes, it's a good investment.
- [GUESTS CHATTERING]
[ISOBEL] I'm telling you,
I saw the place already.
Don't just keep those money.
[ISOBEL] You should invest
in us already.
[CLICKS TONGUE] You know,
[GROANS]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [JACKET RUSTLES]
my life will actually be
in danger
with everything that Boss Arnel
is making me do.
I just can't stomach that we're
fabricating the truth.
Dude, that's what
the boss likes.
He knows what the masses wants.
They'll think you're a coward.
And you'll return
to how it was before.
And if that's what you want,
you'll go back to zero.
Of course I'm not going
to waste this opportunity.
- As you should! [LAUGHING]
- Hey, watch it.
My bad. I know, I know.
We'll definitely
get a raise now!
Come on, Salvador,
if you don't do this,
you'll go back to how you were.
Poor as hell.
Oh, Oli, I am not poor.
Sir, Mr. Chan was almost killed
by Victor Zafra.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
We've already put them
in separate cells.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Victor tried to kill me!
My life is in danger!
I don't think you know just what
kind of man Victor Zafra is.
They will not stop...
until you're dead.
So do something! Protect me!
I have my rights!
If you want to live,
cooperate with us.
Be a state witness
against Victor Zaffra.
We'll protect you
under witness protection
but you have to tell us
everything you know.
Until that syndicate
is not dissolved,
you're not safe.
You are not a free man
right now.
But you are free...
to choose your fate.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR DOORS OPENING]
[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
- [KAREN] It still hurts.
- [SEBASTIAN CHUCKLES]
[KAREN] Sorry, sir.
Alright, listen up.
I'd like to remind everyone.
We're here to have a good time.
Okay? Let's have fun.
Let's forget about everything
that happened.
It's just really hard
to accept it.
[SEBASTIAN] And that's why
we're here!
Let's just drink it all away,
okay?
- How about it, Sam?
-I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Don't let me ruin your night.
- Okay.
- Ma'am Sam,
if you want to rest, we can do
this some other time.
[RALLOS] You'll just go crazy
thinking about it.
Let's just go inside. Come on!
- Let's go then!
- Woohoo!
Let's go!
- Hey, Ron!
- Sir Seb!
- Your table's ready.
- Very good!
- Lead the way.
- Good.
Yes, yes, yo!
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[RALLOS] Good job!
- Oh, Karen, sit here.
- Oh.
- So it's comfortable for you.
- Here, Sam.
[ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BINOY] Whoa!
- [TEKLA] This is the place?!
You should've told me!
I would've worn my heels.
Oh, you!
Let's go back
to the diner then.
- Whoa, hey! I'm just joking!
- No way!
Come on, Gabo.
It's not everyday that we get
to drink at a place like this.
Let's make the most of it
plus...
you got 10,000 pesos anyway.
Finally! A meal
that's not pagpag!
- [LAUGHS]
- Gabo, I'm parched!
I'm finally getting some booze!
- Cold beer!
- [LAUGHTER]
As for me, Gabo, I'm starving.
As if you aren't all the time!
Even stale and burnt rice
end up in your stomach!
Don't worry, guys.
I'll feed you real good grub!
And I'll make sure you'll drown
in booze tonight.
[LAUGHTER, CHEERING]
Looks like there's a lot
of people today.
Show us how you'll throw up.
- [FAKE GAGS]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- Oh.
- Table for how many, sir?
Uh, for seven.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
That bastard Delgado
is way too arrogant.
Who does he think he is?!
Back in my day,
he was just a low-level agent!
I suspect he's targeting Victor
because he knows he's my son.
That bastard will get
his payback soon.
- Arturo.
- Ma'am.
Dig into Director Delgado's
background.
I'm sure we can use
something against him.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll take care of it.
Ma.
How's Victor doing?
He's miserable!
He doesn't belong there.
Ma, we need to get Victor
out of there!
If we need to storm the NCIA
to break him out,
I'll do it, Ma!
Lucas, calm down!
This is not the time
for you to be rash.
You have to think.
And think smart.
[STAFF] I'm sorry, sir.
There's no space inside anymore.
However, there are
tables available outside.
- What?
- But it's hot here!
- We just cleared a table.
- There's no air conditioning.
[BINOY] We should've stayed
at home!
Cut the dramatics, as if
you aren't used to the heat.
[TOLITS] Fine.
At least the food is good.
Don't worry.
The food here is good.
[TOLITS] C'mon,
we should order.
Gabo.
Thank you.
We know your cut from
that gig was small,
but you still managed
to treat us.
C'mon, guys.
I'm actually the one feeling
embarrassed around you guys.
I wasn't even able to share
my cut with you guys
from my second mission.
So even if it's
just ten thousand,
lat least I was able
to make it up to you guys.
[IPE] It's alright, Gabo.
We weren't with you
on your second mission.
Our agreement was that if
we joined you on the mission,
we get a fifty percent cut
of your earnings.
- [BONG] What was your mission?
- [BINOY] Was it dangerous?
[TOLITS] We went up against
big shots on our first mission.
[DABOY] You're right.
They had big guns.
You know what,
my second mission
was even harder.
I've had to deal with
bigger syndicates.
Even the NCIA was involved.
The NCIA was there?!
They were also there
on our first mission, right?
Yeah, they were
the ones who fired first.
That's why there was
a shootout inside the bar.
Hey, wait a minute.
Thank God your mission
was a success.
[SEBASTIAN] We'll have
seven beers for now.
Very good, very good.
Thank you.
[CASTOR SIGHS] We really went
through a lot, didn't we?
I couldn't even imagine
that we went up against
a big syndicate.
[KAREN] I almost died!
[ROBERT] Seems like
they were ready for us.
This group is definitely bigger
than Victor Zafra's crew.
[BORROMEO] What matters
now is that
they didn't get
the upper hand on us.
We have Mr. Chan.
[GABO] When
they started fighting,
that's when I sneaked in
to get the gold.
What? Did you say gold?
Do you have the gold?
How much gold
do you have, Gabo?
That must've been worth
a lot of money!
You can say that again.
We saw it at the bar!
- [TOLITS] Was it a lot?
- Yes.
They only gave you
one hundred thousand?
[TEKLA] He's right.
Two hundred thousand pesos.
But one hundred thousand
of that was a bonus
for returning the gold.
[SAM] That's the thing.
We already caught Mr. Chan,
but we ended up
in this situation.
[RALLOS] Ma'am Pia has
her eyes on you, Ma'am Sam.
Apart from that,
Sir Delgado is pissed at you.
Don't worry about that.
I will take care
of all of you.
I'll talk to Delgado.
It'll be fine.
[BONG] That's a shame,
Gabo.
You should've run away
with the gold.
You would've gotten out
of Ginintuang Lupa by now.
You and your whole family.
C'mon, Gabo isn't like you!
Even if he's like that,
his conscience is clean.
[IPE] I respect you, Gabo.
You're so different from us.
If that were me, I would've
run away with the gold.
Gabo, what happened
to the NCIA?
Did they recognize you?
[KAREN] We'll definitely get
in trouble sooner or later.
If Sam gets suspended,
what if we get suspended
and get laid off from work too?
That sounds nicer.
But what you did was illegal.
They might be looking for you!
Don't drag us with you!
They won't.
They didn't see me because
I escaped right away.
So don't worry.
We are safe.
[TEKLA] That's right.
I think it's best if we order.
The waiter keeps
on ignoring me.
I'm starving!
[IPE] Waiter!
[TOLITS] Where are they?
[BINOY] The place is packed.
Maybe they're inside.
It's fine.
I'll go to the bar to order.
- [IPE] You don't have to.
- [TOLITS] Thank you!
[BINOY] One ice-cold
beer, please.
You've got some serious nerve.
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA"
BY JUAN KARLOS PLAYING]
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA" CONTINUES]
[ROMY] What do you plan,
Paquito?
Want us
to beat him up ourselves?
Let's wait for Umali's orders.
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- For pete's sake, Paquito.
The job's so simple,
yet you still failed?
The match isn't over, Umali.
If you want, Romy and I
will finish it.
Come out here
before I lose my patience!
[LINE DROPS]
[PHONE TURNS OFF]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Django, come with us.
Explain to Umali what happened.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA"
BY JUAN KARLOS PLAYING]
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA" CONTINUES]
They did mug Salvador.
But that bastard became bolder.
Aren't you cops?
You can handle that!
You know,
you reek of arrogance.
You're too proud when
you're nothing like your father.
Go on, shoot me!
Let's see how brave you are.
Challenge all those criminals,
and ask them how much they are!
Here comes
- Salvador "The Vindicator"!
Bring it on! [GROWLS]
You know, Sam, I was thinking,
why don't we go on vacation?
Anywhere we can unwind!
Somewhere far away
from our problems.
Somewhere far away from here.
I know you. You're the three
bastards from Chinatown.
Why? Will you fight back?
Wanna taste my punch?
- [BLOW LANDS]
- That's it?
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
If they file a complaint
against us,
we might end up suspended!
- Gabo, help us!
- Some NCIA guys beat us up!
We might be able
to catch up to them, Gabo!
Come on, come on!
Let's catch up to them!
Hurry!